If you come to me at this moment your minutes will become hours your
hours will become days and your days will become a lifetime.
Ashes and Snow is a documentary, drama film directed by Gregory Colbert.
Ashes and Snow, a film by Gregory Colbert, uses both still and movie cameras to
explore extraordinary interactions between humans and animals.
The 60-minute feature is a poetic narrative rather than a documentary.
It aims to lift the natural and artificial barriers between humans and other
species, dissolving the distance that exists between them.
Narrator (voice), played by Laurence Fishburne.
Ashes and Snow by Canadian artist Gregory Colbert is an installation of photographic artworks, films, and a novel in
letters that travels in the Nomadic Museum, a temporary structure built exclusively to house the exhibition.
The work explores the shared poetic sensibilities of human beings and animals.
Ashes and Snow has traveled to Venice, New York City,
Santa Monica, Tokyo, and Mexico City.
To date, Ashes and Snow has attracted more than 10 million visitors, making it
the most attended exhibition by a living artist in history.
The film explores themes of elephant, photographer, art, animals.
The tone is emotional.